https://www.theforgivenessproject.com/terms-and-conditions/

The Forgiveness Project Privacy Policy
The Forgiveness Project is committed to protecting your privacy. We operate in accordance with the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) 2018 and the Freedom of Information Act 2000. The Forgiveness Project will never distribute or sell your personal data to any third party.
We collect and process the following data about you:
Information that you provide through Mailchimp when subscribing to our newsletters. This information is only used so that we can provide you with our newsletter and will not be used for any other purposes.
Information that you provide when you download our education resources (through Mailchimp). This is so we can request feedback regarding our education resources, provide and improve our service to you, provide updates and news relating to our education resources.
Information you provide through Eventbrite when booking an event or training course. This is so we can provide the appropriate event organisation and management.
Information you provide when responding to a survey through our website. This information will only be used for the purpose outlined with each survey.
If you contact us, we keep a record of that correspondence.
When you make a payment on our website through paypal, we keep a record of it.
Where we store your personal data:
Information you provide via our newsletter provider Mailchimp is held on Mailchimp. See here for their privacy statement.
Information you provide via Eventbrite is held on Eventbrite. See here for their privacy statement.
Information you provide when you download our education resources is held on Mailchimp. See here for their privacy statement.
Information you provide when you fill in a survey is stored on our secure website platform.
Information you provide through our website platform, Mailchimp or Eventbrite may be transferred and stored on to our password protected secure server.
We keep a record of donations and purchases made on our site on our secure website platform and our password protected secure server. We do not store your payment details. These are processed and stored by our payment provider Paypal. See their privacy policy here. Your payment will also be recorded in our secure online accounting software, Quickbooks.
Please note that we will send you a ‘Thank you’ as a receipt of your donation. If you do not opt in to receive communications you will not receive any further communications from us beyond this point.
Tracking our visitors
We use Google Analytics including Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting to monitor how people use our websites and aggregates general statistics about customers, traffic patterns and related site information in an anonymous form. Any demographic reports produced using this data will be used to determine a better understanding of our website traffic and visitor needs and tailor future content and functionality.
Cookies
This website uses cookies. A cookie is a small file placed on your computer by a website. See our cookie policy.
If you are concerned about the use of cookies, we suggest you set your browser’s privacy settings to ‘high’. This setting will block cookies that collect personal information without your explicit consent while allowing you to fully enjoy the features of the websites. Depending on your web browser, you may also be able to block or delete specific cookies using browser tools or settings.
Changes to our privacy policy
Any changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by email.
If you have any other questions about this policy please contact us at info@theforgivenessproject.com.
If you have read any of our stories or our work has helped you in any way, please consider making a donation today. Your support directly helps us continue sharing real-life stories of forgiveness across the world.
QUICK LINKS
Subscribe to Newsletter About Us Privacy Policy Cookie PolicyJOIN OUR COMMUNITYCONTACTTel: +44 (0)20 7821 0035
E-mail: info@theforgivenessproject.com
The Forgiveness Project
10 Buckingham Palace Road
London SW1W 0QP
UK
Registered Charity Number: 1103922
COPYRIGHT© 2020 The Forgiveness Project.
The Forgiveness Project is unaffiliated to any religion or religious entity, and owns the intellectual property rights for all images and text on this website, which should not be reproduced in any shape or form without express permission.
This website uses cookies to improve your experience. We'll assume you're ok with this, but you can opt-out if you wish. Cookie settingsACCEPTPrivacy & Cookies Policy
Close
Privacy Overview
This website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these cookies, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may have an effect on your browsing experience.
Necessary
Necessary
Always Enabled
Necessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. This category only includes cookies that ensures basic functionalities and security features of the website. These cookies do not store any personal information.
Non-necessary
Non-necessary
Any cookies that may not be particularly necessary for the website to function and is used specifically to collect user personal data via analytics, ads, other embedded contents are termed as non-necessary cookies. It is mandatory to procure user consent prior to running these cookies on your website.
This website uses cookies to improve your experience. We'll assume you're ok with this, but you can opt-out if you wish.
Read More
Accept
Decline
Cookie Settings
I consent to the use of following cookies:
Necessary
Marketing
Analytics
Preferences
Unclassified
Cookie Declaration
About Cookies
Necessary (1)
Marketing (4)
Analytics (0)
Preferences (0)
Unclassified (2)
Necessary cookies help make a website usable by enabling basic functions like page navigation and access to secure areas of the website. The website cannot function properly without these cookies.
Name
Domain
Purpose
Expiry
Type
wpl_user_preference
www.theforgivenessproject.com
WP GDPR Cookie Consent Preferences
1 year
HTTP
Marketing cookies are used to track visitors across websites. The intention is to display ads that are relevant and engaging for the individual user and thereby more valuable for publishers and third party advertisers.
Name
Domain
Purpose
Expiry
Type
VISITOR_INFO1_LIVE
youtube.com
Google advertising domain.
Session
HTTP
YSC
youtube.com
Google advertising domain.
Session
HTTP
GPS
youtube.com
Google advertising domain
Session
HTTP
IDE
doubleclick.net
Google advertising cookie used for user tracking and ad targeting purposes
2 years
HTTP
Analytics cookies help website owners to understand how visitors interact with websites by collecting and reporting information anonymously.
We do not use cookies of this type.
Preference cookies enable a website to remember information that changes the way the website behaves or looks, like your preferred language or the region that you are in.
We do not use cookies of this type.
Unclassified cookies are cookies that we are in the process of classifying, together with the providers of individual cookies.
Name
Domain
Purpose
Expiry
Type
cookielawinfo-checkbox-necessary
www.theforgivenessproject.com
---
---
Cookies are small text files that can be used by websites to make a user's experience more efficient. The law states that we can store cookies on your device if they are strictly necessary for the operation of this site. For all other types of cookies we need your permission. This site uses different types of cookies. Some cookies are placed by third party services that appear on our pages.
Cookie Settings
Go to Top
